{
    "subject": "resource/Feline_Frame-Up",
    "predicate": "property/releaseDate",
    "object": "1954-02-13",
    "human_readable": "The release date of Feline Frame-Up is 1954-02-13.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9830242395401001,
            "question": "Is the release date of Feline Frame-Up February 13th, 1954?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9087355732917786,
            "question": "Provide the date of release for Feline Frame-Up."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8763489723205566,
            "question": "What is the release date of Feline Frame-Up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8513447642326355,
            "question": "When was Feline Frame-Up released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8397992849349976,
            "question": "In what year was Feline Frame-Up released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7975602746009827,
            "question": "What year is associated with the release of Feline Frame-Up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7587282061576843,
            "question": "On what specific date did Feline Frame-Up come out?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7011852264404297,
            "question": "When did Feline Frame-Up premiere?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6963788866996765,
            "question": "What month and day was Feline Frame-Up released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3971214294433594,
            "question": "Is Feline Frame-Up a movie?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The release date of Feline Frame-Up is 1954-02-13.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1172_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What month and day was Feline Frame-Up released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1172_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Feline Frame-Up premiere?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1172_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=On what specific date did Feline Frame-Up come out?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1172_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1172_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1172_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1172_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1172_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1172_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1172_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1172_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1172_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1172_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1172_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe query about the release date of \"Feline Frame-Up\" being February 13, 1954, is correctly supported by the documents provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}